ISAAC WEISS

Auburn, AL (334) 748-1379 weissic@icloud.com

isaacweiss.dev github.com/icweiss22 linkedin.com/in/icweiss22

SKILLS

- Web Development: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, knockout.js, DataTables, AJAX
- Languages: C#, C++, Java, Python, Swift, SQL
- Tools: .NET ecosystem, Visual Studio, VS Code, SSMS
- Collaboration: GitHub, Teams, Jira, Service Now
- Other: Entity Framework, LINQ, Razor

EDUCATION

Auburn University

Samuel Ginn College of Engineering Auburn, AL B.S., Computer Science

Concentration: Business

Minor: French

August 2019 - December 2023

GPA: 3.97/4.00

Dean's List 2019 - 2023 Scholarships: Spirit of Auburn Presidential Scholarship | ADTRAN | Bonnie Arnall

French Club Treasurer

SUMMARY

Auburn University senior majoring in Computer Science with a Business concentration and a French minor. Very passionate about software engineering, with experience in web development using the .NET ecosystem. Familiar with back-end (SSMS, SQL), middleware (.NET, C#), and front-end (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) tools.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, *Campus Web Solutions* Auburn, AL (May 2021 – now)

Full-stack co-op at a web development firm specializing in developing robust web applications for Auburn University.

- Designed, developed, and maintained 30+ of Auburn University's most used web applications using strict coding regulations and security practices, including their Vaccine and Pharmacy Scheduler, Board of Trustees Voting System, and Event Ticketing System.
- Leveraged an array of web development tools including HTML, CSS, .NET Framework, jQuery, C#, Visual Studio, and SSMS to create dynamic and robust digital solutions.
- Guided other co-ops by assuming a mentorship role, conducting live practice sessions, and authoring a comprehensive web development guide.
- Actively participated in client meetings, effectively communicating technical concepts, and proposing innovative ideas that garnered client approval.
- Implemented agile development methodologies to streamline project workflows, tracking and managing 100+ deliverables with precision using Jira, resulting in timely project completions.
- Prioritized mobile responsiveness, crafting applications that seamlessly adapt across diverse devices. Conducted comprehensive runtime analyses and eliminating performance bottlenecks.
- Led the end-to-end redesign and development initiative for the Auburn University Vice President of Research's site pages (cws.auburn.edu/ovpr), creating a dynamic backend system empowering the client to effortlessly update and manage content.

Exchange Student, Toulon, France (January – June 2023)

• Fostered a diverse global perspective by immersing myself deeply in the local culture while honing language proficiency.

Hackathon Logistics Coordinator, Auburn, AL (September 2019 – February 2020)

• Contributed to the success of a memorable 24-hour Hackathon competition by managing scheduling of staff, managing room assignments and activities, communicating with vendors, and coordinating food services with caterers.

Front Service Clerk, *Publix* Auburn, AL (June 2018 – October 2020)

• Efficiently processed customer transactions as cashier and bagger while maintaining a friendly and approachable demeanor.